You're still saying that?
I'll crush you!
King of the pirates, don't make me laugh.
Why did his attack look on me?
A new Haki must be the technique
that old man taught him.
His punches can hurt kaido,
but there's gotta be a trick.
What the hell is it?
We might just win this—that's nice
and all—but before I do anything,
there's something I gotta
get straight with Straw Hats.
Hey, shrimp, you don't even know?
even know What it means to be King of the
Pirates is not something you take lightly.
So stop running your mouth.
He kicked his ass in Curry.
How did he get so much stronger?
Few can stand up to me.
And they are not to be underestimated.
I know you didn't come here just to lose.
Are you telling me you think
you're as good as them?
Answer me, Straw Hat!
Thunderbogwar!
Damn it!
I saw that one coming,
but he's fast! Well done.
It's an improvement over
last time, if nothing else.
Come on, Kaido!
Honestly, practice
meant to be incinerated!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama?
I'll burn you to ash, boy!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hair badly! Ah!
Foxfire style!
Flameran!
Oh!
He got Prometheus right in half!
Ha-ha-ha!
That's Kittymon's move!
Nice one, Zoro!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I stole it!
Oh-oh-oh-oh!
I'm gonna make you pay!
Don't lower your guard, Luffy!
You're dealing with two emperors!
Shambles.
Straw Hat, get up.
Traffy!
Thanks, you saved me!
Listen, because there's something
you and I need to get straight.
Those samurai—I was gonna teleport them to
safety anyway—before you
said a damn word to me,
but you just had to bark orders.
Do you
know how that made me look?
Taking orders from you
like a damn subordinate!
damn subordinate
Huh?
Why would anyone care about that?
That's the idea, right?
You followed Straw Hat's orders
to show your loyalty to him?
Of course not!
Just a loser with a loser underling.
You two were made for each other.
You're the loser, you big stupid jerk!
Was that directed at me?
You can squabble on
your own damn time. Ah!
You're just for me, the astronaut!
Yes, Mama!
Heavenly Baba!
Okay, here's the deal! Huh?
The first person who
dodges her attack, loses!
Who would agree to that crap?
You're a Gates man and you're
still pulling this nonsense?
Go ahead and die!
You don't have what it takes
to make it with real pirates!
You're blinded!
You're losers and I win!
Ah! Whatever.
Suit yourselves. I'm not playing.
But if you're not playing, then
why are you still standing here?
Yeah, you wusses! Just go!
Hey! Watch out!
Why did you all just stand there?
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
What a pity.
So much for being King of the Pirates.
Now the fun part.
How am I gonna murder
you rotten rats? Who?
Give me a sec, Lin-Lin.
I want to see how strong
these kids are, hmm,
that seems like a waste
of time, you stay back!
He took Kitty Kamazo, huh, huh?
You think that mask fooled me?
I'd know that laugh anywhere
if I had these punishers!
When we fought, you'd be dead.
Zoro Giri.
I seriously doubt that.
Beheading Claw!
Three swords die.
Purgatory!
Onigiri!
It's not enough.
That wasn't half bad.
I need to unleash a little
more of your power, Enma.
What do you say?
Kaido! Hmm?
We're gonna finish you in one shot.
Fourth gear!
For the Feltzman!
No!
Let's run!
I'm rotten!
Now, Rue, and Tapas.
Each of you a monster in your own right.
Just as it should be.
Let's see if you have what it
takes to be king of the pirates.
I won't hold back!
Come on!
No!
Ugh, that stung.
Not a bad start.
I probably couldn't break
your next skin if I tried,
but that doesn't mean I can't crush
you to death with enough pressure!
You want to see me at my worst, I'm
happy to get you a front row seat!
Fuck me!
That's not bad, but it needs
more mass to seal the deal.
More mass?
Let's try this, then.
What the hell? Now, attack!
Crap!
You bastard!
You were gonna take me
out too, weren't you?
Damn, that hurt.
You're really trying to bury me.
I remember that feeling.
Reminds me of the good ol' day.
Yummy yum.
All charged and ready to go.
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
Here I thought you were all talk.
That wasn't half bad!
If you're crazy enough to
aim for King of the Pirates,
that's the least I can expect.
And yet, none of you have
any hope of stopping me!
Almost breaks my heart.
We've come this far, but you'll
all be dead in no time at all.
And I'll take so much
more than just your life.
Like any good pirate, I'll take all
your crew members who followed you here.
No way in hell!
I'll never let you!
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma!
Not just your crew members.
We'll take all of your treasures, too.
You've got some punoglyphs, right?
A fair prize for what you put me through.
I can't wait.
Didn't think about treasure.
I'd be happy to take yours!
Whoever wins this battle will be one
step closer to being king of the pirates.
Yeah, you're right about
that and it's gonna be me.
DEMOLITION DUST.
They were just scraps anyway.
You idiots will never
be king of the pirates.
But at least you can
entertain me before you die!
The land of Wano is mine!
I will bring a new era!
Can you carry the weight for me?
Will you deliver this country?
What?
What does it belong to you?
Kong, Kong!
Kong, rifle!
Take it a nap, Mr. Emperor?
Then this is your wake of call.
I'm...
I'm... I'm...
No room.
And shambles.
Never seen an anatomical
chart of a dragon before.
But your heart should be here!
Give a knife!
If I can't beat you from the
outside, I'll do it from within!
You're quite the pest.
See if you've done your research.
If you know how durable I am.
Maybe you're not as stupid.
As I thought you were.
Those scales of yours are
a real pain in the ass.
But I know a trick to get inside too.
Scyther!
Sonic!
That one hurt, didn't it?
Now die!
As long as you're under the
open sky, you're my prey.
You didn't think you could
escape from me, did you?
I admit, my expectations weren't
exactly high, but this has been fun.
I know! Schneider!
Look at you.
Not bad.
Hey, Traffy!
Teleport me up there and hurry!
What?
I'm not a moving service, and
I don't take orders from you!
I'll do it because I want to,
not because you told me to!
Foxfire style!
Glass bread!
Flame red!
Thanks, Zoro!
Let's try again!
Traffy!
Huh?
I told you!
Stop acting like you're my boss, dammit!
What the hell?
Out of the way, Kaido!
That's no ordinary weapon he's got!
One sword style!
Blood! Dragon! Blaze!
What is this power I feel?
How?
Why is Odin's presence in his sword?
Tang it!
I missed you!
This is what you get
for taking us lightly!
Indra!
Zoro!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
Look at that!
All lined up for me!
Heaven's wrath, god of
lightning tension, heed my call!
That woman is a living calamity!
What in the hell?!
How did you survive all that
lightning without a scratch on you?!
Tush!
I'm a robber man!
Huh?
You're gonna pay for hurting my friends!
Blast friends!
Fire doesn't work either.
Why the hell not?
Cause God!
Come out!
Got me!
AAAAAA!